( BIRDS CHIRPING )
( DOG BARKING )
( MARGARET SCREAMS )
( PANTS )
Help .
Help me !
( SCREAMS )
( PANTING )
( INDISTINCT MUMBLING )
( SCREAMING )
Help me , Lord .
I 'm dying .
What is this ?
Cancer ?
( GROANING )
( SCREAMING )
Mother Mary , full of grace , protect me
and guide me in my hour of death .
( SCREAMS )
( GASPING )
( GASPS )
( GURGLES )
( COOING )
It 's a test .
Cut it down .
( COOING )
( CRYING )
Shh .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
( GIRLS LAUGHING )
( LAUGHS )
DESJARDIN : Sue Snell and Tommy Ross , come on .
( GASPS )
( BLOWS WHISTLE )
Let 's go , ladies ! In the water ! Caps on , please !
Chris and Sue , let 's go !
( GIRL GRUNTS )
( WHISTLE BLOWING )
DESJARDIN : I want you to keep it in the air three times . All right ?
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
CHRIS : We are graduating , Ms. Desjardin .
Yeah , Sue ! ( ALL CHEERING )
Get that .
Don 't be afraid of the ball , ladies .
All right , here we go .
( WHISTLE BLOWING )
All right , Carrie White . Let 's get Carrie into the game .
You can 't stand on the sidelines all the time . Come on .
GIRL : Whoo !
Carrie 's serve .
CHRIS : Yeah , Carrie White !
Do it , Carrie ! Yeah , yeah .
Throw it . Do it . Serve it .
Oh . Ow . ( GASPS )
( BOTH GASP )
( ALL LAUGHING )
What the hell ?
( LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY )
It 's so funny , Chris .
CHRIS : Are you okay ? Yeah .
( LAUGHING )
CHRIS : Oh , my God . ( CHUCKLES )
You eat shit .
( ALL LAUGHING )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
SUE : No , he didn 't . CHRIS : Yes , he did .
No , he didn 't . You 're making it up .
He came up to me and I said , " Well , you have to extend your hand ... "
Now you 're lying .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
( SQUEAKING )
( PANTS )
( BREATH TREMBLING )
Help ! Help ! Help me !
Help me .
Get off me , you freak ! Please .
Oh , my God . Look what you did to my shirt .
Please !
Stop ! Stop ! Settle down .
I think I 'm bleeding to death . Please .
Oh , my God . It 's period blood .
I 'm bleeding . I think I 'm dying .
What ? Oh , my God .
Please help me !
It 's just your period .
Just plug it up .
Help me ! Oh , God !
Oh ! She got you . ( SOBBING ) Help me !
God , just plug it up !
Help !
ALL : ( CHANTING ) Plug it up !
I 'm sorry . No !
( CHANTING CONTINUES )
No !
ALL : Plug it up !
( SCREAMING )
( WHIMPERING )
( CHANTING CONTINUES )
DESJARDIN : Girls , come on ! Move !
Ladies .
Oh , my God . Okay . All right . Help me .
Okay , honey , stand up . Let 's get you cleaned up .
Help me , help me .
Oh , Carrie , come on .
DESJARDIN : Stand up . Come on , can you stand up ?
CARRIE : It hurts ! It hurts !
It hurts ! Something 's not right . Something 's not right .
Okay , okay . What are you talking about ?
Ms. Desjardin , I don 't think she knows it 's her period .
No !
All right , Sue . Get out of here ! You 're not helping .
No ! No ! Calm down !
( ALL GASP )
Everyone get out ! Now ! Out !
Okay , deep breaths . Come here .
Come on . It 's okay . You 're okay , sweetie .
It 's totally normal .
Shh .
Do you know what it means ?
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ) ( SCREAMS )
Okay , sweetie .
( SCHOOL BELL RINGING )
Are you , uh , feeling better ?
Can I get you some aspirin ?
Some juice or something ? ( GASPS )
DESJARDIN : Juice ? Really , Henry ?
MORTON : Maybe you just want us to leave you alone .
Carrie , honey , I am so sorry that I slapped you .
I should have handled it better .
It 's totally normal for young girls to get their periods .
It usually actually happens a little bit earlier .
Is this your first time ?
( SIGHS )
Honey , do you understand what 's happening to your body ?
Do you know what it means ?
CARRIE : What ?
I don 't know . I felt something moving down there .
DESJARDIN : Oh , honey . Whoa !
Maybe you could , uh , talk to a counselor about that
or a nurse .
Um , what I need to know is who started throwing
things .
It was Chris Hargensen and all of her friends .
Cassie ... " Carrie . "
Carrie , did Chris Hargensen start this ?
Honey , you don 't have to protect them .
What they did was unforgiveable .
Okay , uh ...
It doesn 't seem that Carrie is going to point the finger ,
so Ms. Desjardin , I need you to get to the bottom of this .
Let the punishment fit the crime .
Okay .
Carrie , you 're excused from P.E. class for the rest of the week .
Just take study hall , okay ? At the library .
MORTON : Yeah . We 're going to have to call your mom .
What ?
We 're going to have to call your mother , Carrie .
I know she 's had problems with us in the past ,
ever since the state stopped her from
homeschooling you anymore ,
but we 've got to bring her into this , okay ?
Mmm-mmm . No .
Sweetie , we have no choice .
We have to tell your mom what happened . No .
( GASPING )
DESJARDIN : Carrie .
BOY : Hey . Hey , you .
( SCHOOL BELL RINGING )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
( BOYS CHUCKLING )
( SIGHS )
( GASPS )
Tina , give it to me . Give it here .
This is brilliant . Look at this video .
GALS : ( CHANTING ) Plug it up !
She got her period . On my hand . ( LAUGHS )
CHRIS : That is so disgusting .
It was on my hand and Sue 's shirt . It was so disgusting .
( CHUCKLING )
Mmm .
I 'm sorry you had to come to school today , Mom .
( BRAKES SQUEAK )
( ENGINE RATTLES )
Let 's go inside , little girl .
You need to come inside with me .
Mama , why didn 't you tell me ?
I was so scared , Mama . I thought I was going to die .
Mama , they laughed at me and they threw things at me .
We 'll talk about this inside , Carrie .
No .
I want to talk about it right here .
I don 't want to go inside with you .
( DOOR CREAKS OPEN )
( GASPS ) Crazy Carrie , Crazy Carrie ! ( SNORTS )
( SIGHS )
Crazy Carrie , Crazy Carrie .
( GRUNTS )
( PANTING )
( THUDDING )
MARGARET : Oh , Lord , help my child .
She 's lost .
Mama , stop it .
Mama !
I don 't want to upset you .
So , you 're a woman now .
And God made Eve from the rib of Adam .
And what , Carrie ? Say it . No , Mama .
Say it . Talk to me .
Please just talk to me . And Eve was weak .
I just want you to talk to me .
And the first sin was the sin of intercourse .
Why didn 't you tell me , Mama ?
And God visited Eve with a curse .
And the curse was a curse of blood .
I 'm not going to say that .
That 's not even in the Bible . It doesn 't say that anywhere .
Oh , Lord . Help this little girl see the sin of her days and ways .
Show her if she had remained innocent ,
the curse of blood would not have come upon her as it did on Eve .
I 'm not Eve , Mama . I didn 't sin .
You showered with those other girls .
You had lust-filled thoughts .
Everyone has to shower , Mama . Everyone . That 's just the rules .
You must be different , because He can see you .
I don 't want to be different , Mama . I want to be like them .
He can smell the sin on you .
And He will punish you . ( GASPS )
I will not let that come down upon you . I will not .
Lord have mercy .
No . " The Lord is good . His unfailing love endures forever ,
" and his faithfulness continues through all generations . "
Psalms 100 , verse 5 .
I 'm going to keep you away from that school .
You can 't . We 'll pray . We 'll pray together .
To save our women-weak , wicked , sinning souls .
You didn 't tell me and they laughed .
I didn 't sin , you sinned .
I did not .
I did not sin .
Go to your closet .
No , Mama .
Go to your closet and pray .
You pray .
No .
( YELLS ) No !
No !
Get off me ! Mama ! Stop it ! ( SCREAMS )
Go to your closet and pray for forgiveness .
No !
You pray . Mama ! Help !
( SCREAMING )
No , Mommy ! Come on .
Please ! Help ! ( GRUNTS )
You pray , little girl . Pray for forgiveness .
Mommy , let me go !
Let me out !
( BANGING ON DOOR )
( SCREAMING )
Mom !
God , you suck !
( GASPS )
( CREAKING )
( SOFTLY ) Help me . Help me .
( CARRIE BREATHING HEAVILY )
( WHIMPERS )
( MUSIC PLAYING )
( KISSING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
What ?
I 'm sorry . What ?
Hey . What 's wrong ?
I really messed up today , Tommy .
What , that thing with Carrie ?
You know about that ?
Yeah , everyone knows about it ,
but you 're not responsible for what Chris does .
Yeah , but it was me , too .
You threw tampons at Carrie White ?
I kicked a kid in the ribs once .
Yeah , while he was knocked out .
Because this kid ,
he used to beat the living shit out of me every day in sixth grade .
Danny Patrick .
( CHUCKLES )
Did you apologize to Carrie ?
( SCOFFS ) Did you apologize to Danny Patrick ?
No , but we 're not in sixth grade anymore .
( CHUCKLING ) Don 't .
He was a dick to me . ( CHUCKLING )
What did Carrie White ever do to you ?
CHRIS : Whoo !
And that , ladies and gentlemen , is why he lost his license .
TINA : ( LAUGHS ) Then why are you still driving ?
I don 't need a license if they can 't catch me .
Jackie 's email , Jackie 's email !
( BOTH LAUGHING )
Chris no . No !
Wow . Why don 't you two kiss or something while you 're at it ?
( BILLY CHUCKLES )
Oh , baby .
( CHUCKLES )
Don 't be stupid .
( MOANING )
Wait .
Do you think we 're going to get detention because of that ?
Because that would suck . No .
They should be thanking us for helping her through her first period .
I got her a tampon . So what ?
You were only trying to help her , right ?
We should post it .
( LAUGHS )
No , I 'm in it .
No one 's going to see you , Teenie .
What ? ( CHUCKLES ) What are you doing ?
Carrie White .
CHRIS : Favorite movie ?
BILLY : Bloodsport .
( LAUGHS )
TINA : Favorite drink ?
Bloody Mary . ( TINA CHUCKLES )
MARGARET : ( SINGING ALONG TO RECORD ) Brightly beams
Our Father 's mercy
From His lighthouse evermore
But to us He gives the keeping
Of the lights along the shore
Let the lower lights be burning
( CONTINUES SINGING )
( DOOR CREAKING )
Did you finish your prayers , little girl ?
Yes , Mama .
That 's my good girl .
( KISSES )
I love you .
I love you , too , Mama .
( CHUCKLES )
( WHISTLE BLOWING ) DESJARDIN : All right , stand up .
Line up , please .
( WHISTLE BLOWING )
DESJARDIN : You have a big week coming up . A big month , actually .
Probably the biggest month of your lives . Prom and then graduation .
Are you excited ? ( GIRLS CHUCKLE )
You probably all have your dresses .
You have your dates by now .
What about you , Chris ?
Who 's the lucky guy ?
Billy Nolan . You don 't know him .
He doesn 't go to this school .
Are you going to get him a boutonniere ?
Or are you just going to pin a bloody tampon to his lapel ?
I so don 't need to hear this .
You 're not going anywhere .
What about you , Sue ?
Are you and Tommy busy campaigning to be Prom King and Queen ?
I would have voted for you .
Not now .
You all did a shitty thing yesterday .
A really shitty thing .
And one of you had the audacity to post a video .
Somebody made a video of it ?
This is bullshit .
That 's it . Thanks to Miss Hargensen , you 're all running suicides .
I 'm not doing it .
That 's up to you .
That 's up to all of you , but anyone who stops running is suspended .
And if you 're suspended , you 're not going to prom .
While you 're running , I 'd like for you to think long and hard
about what it would be like to be Carrie White .
( SCHOOL BELL RINGING )
I 'll be okay , Mama .
I 'm going to leave work early today and pick you up after school .
( WHISTLE BLOWING )
( ALL PANTING )
She can 't do this to me .
Just let it go , Chris . We 're almost done .
Then every day this week ?
All because of Carrie White ?
Like hell I Will .
DESJARDIN : Keep moving , Hargensen .
Keep running or you 're not going to prom .
Fuck you !
This is child abuse .
What did you say to me ?
I 'm not going to run another goddamn inch
because Carrie White got her period
and was too stupid to know what it was .
What ? DESJARDIN : You 're suspended .
You 're out of prom and you 're out of my class . Now .
No . No ?
You can 't decide that . She can 't do this to us .
Goodbye , Chris . The rest of you , keep at it .
Someone could die of dehydration .
Tina , you have a heart condition , right ?
If we all stick together , they 're not going to suspend all of us .
They 're not going to keep us all from prom . There would be no prom .
Nik , Lizzy ?
DESJARDIN : Let 's go , ladies !
Heather ?
This is bullshit ! We didn 't do anything wrong .
DESJARDIN : All right , let 's go .
Right , Sue ? You 're with me on this , right ?
Come on .
DESJARDIN : Sue .
( BLOWING WHISTLE )
Keep going , ladies .
This isn 't over .
This isn 't over by a long shot .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
GIRL : ( WHISPERS ) That 's Carrie White .
( GIRLS LAUGHING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GASPS )
( EXHALES )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( CHUCKLES )
( DOOR OPENS )
Um , you know ... Sorry .
I was just going to say , you can make it full-screen . Watch .
ULMANN : All right , who 's next ?
Uh , Carrie . Favorite poem . Did you bring one ?
( CHUCKLING )
Yeah .
Why don 't you come to the front of the class
and share it with us all ?
( GIRLS CHUCKLING )
" This unfrequented place to find some ease
" Ease to the body some , none to the mind
" Times past , and what once I was and what am now
" O wherefore was my birth from Heaven foretold
" Twice by an Angel , who at last in sight
" Of both my Parents all in flames ...
" ... ascended . "
( SIGHS )
Okay , uh , that was , uh ...
disturbing . ( ALL CHUCKLE )
ULMANN : That is the most you 've said in class all year .
Is there anything else you 'd like to share
or are you done scaring us for the day ?
Asshole . ( ALL GASP )
ULMANN : Excuse me , Mr. Ross . Did you say something ?
I said , " Awesome . "
I just thought what Carrie read was awesome .
Didn 't you , Mr. Ulmann ?
All right , who 's next ? Uh ...
ULMANN : Nicki .
I mean , Lizzy .
( WHIRRING )
ELEANOR : Is anyone working ?
Excuse me .
( BELL DINGS )
ls anybody working ?
Oh , Margaret .
I 'm sorry to disturb you . I don 't know where Hugo and Gloria ...
Can I help you , Mrs. Snell ? ( CLEARS THROAT )
Yes , I 'm picking up .
( SIGHS )
Margaret , I want to say how sorry I am
about what happened at the school .
There 's no excuse for what Sue did , but she 's a good girl .
Are any of those girls good ?
( CASH REGISTER BEEPING )
Oh , that is beautiful work , Margaret .
Thank you .
I love what you 've done with the neckline .
And the stitches . You can barely see them .
So few people can sew like this anymore .
I could never do anything like this myself .
Sue 's going to look beautiful .
I am so excited for her .
I remember my prom . ( CHUCKLES )
Anyway , she 's going to love it .
These are Godless times , Mrs. Snell .
JOHN : This gym teacher was running Chrissie
into the ground and used profanity .
I believe the term " shitty " was used .
JOHN : She can 't do that . It 's abuse of power .
You 're right , Daddy . That 's what she said .
" Shitty . " She 's really abusive .
Ms. Desjardin was reprimanded for what happened in class today .
But you know we 've had a lot of problems
with your daughter in the past .
And now , with what she did to her classmate , Carrie White .
The girl was having her ...
What your daughter and her posse ...
I 'm not going to sit here and listen to half-truths .
I know my daughter . She said she didn 't do it .
I want her prom privileges restored .
You can 't prove she did anything , can you ?
I believe that there is a video of the incident .
DESJARDIN : And I think your daughter is the one who took it .
I think a video like that would probably
be pretty damning to anyone in it
and to the person who made it .
Don 't you , Mr. Hargensen ?
I don 't know . I 'm just a gym teacher ,
but it seems like a video like that
would probably affect college admissions ,
possibly a lawsuit , tons of bad publicity .
I wonder what The Today Show would do with a video like that .
I think we should just look at her phone and if it 's not there ,
I owe you a huge apology and she should be allowed to go to prom .
Chris .
( CHUCKLES ) Daddy , I 'm not going to give them my phone .
I have personal things on here .
Isn 't that invasion of privacy or something ?
( SIGHS )
Chrissie , if you want to go to prom ,
just give them the damn phone and we can be done with this .
I have to get back to work .
Dad .
God damn it , just give them your phone , Chris .
No .
( SCHOOL BELL RINGING )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
So , I 'm officially out of the prom .
I bet that cocksucker Morton loses his job , though .
My dad is suing him .
Jesus , Sue , why didn 't you stand up for me ?
We could have had them by the balls .
We deserved it for what we did to Carrie White .
I thought I deserved it .
( EXHALES )
Desjardin was right . We did a shitty thing for no reason .
Bullshit !
That Carrie goes around saying that everyone but her and her mother
are going to hell and you stuck up for her ? Come on !
You can be such a pig sometimes , Chris .
What did Carrie White ever do to you ?
She 's been begging for it since the sixth grade , Sue .
I got to go .
I seem to remember you were in there
throwing shit with the rest of us .
What was it that she was calling her ?
" Freak " ? I stopped .
Oh , you stopped ?
Yeah . Why did you keep running ?
Hmm ?
Why did you keep running , Sue ? Stop it , Chris !
You kept running , Sue , little Suze ,
because you 've been dreaming about senior year
and the perfect boyfriend and the perfect prom
your whole goddamned life .
You already booked the hotel ,
already practiced the sounds you 're going to make
when you and Tommy make love . ( PANTING )
( CHUCKLES )
That 's why you had this bullshit change of heart .
You don 't give a shit about Carrie White .
And everybody knows it .
Okay . I 'll see you around , Sue .
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLING )
( CHUCKLING )
Carrie ?
( CREAKING )
( CHUCKLING )
Carrie ?
( GASPS ) ( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
( GRUNTS )
I 'm not going to let anyone hurt you , little girl .
You 're safe here with me .
( SIGHS )
( GASPS )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
Got it .
Hey .
How are you doing ? ( CHUCKLES ) Good .
Good ? Yeah .
What 's up ?
I want you to take Carrie White to prom .
( LAUGHS )
Good one , babe . Come on .
Are you serious ?
I 'm just trying to fix what I did .
( STAMMERING ) Yeah . I get that , but this is ...
Sue , it 's nuts .
Okay , so it 's nuts .
But after what we did to her , I have to do something .
I have to do something that counts .
Uh ...
( CHUCKLING ) What even makes you think that she would say yes to me ?
She 'd say yes .
We 've barely even spoken .
I saw how she looked at you in class when you rescued her .
What girl doesn 't want to go to prom ?
What girl doesn 't want one magical night ?
Maybe I can give that up for her .
No . Babe , I want you to have that magic night .
I don 't want to go to prom with Carrie White .
I want to go to prom with you .
I can 't go .
Hey , Carrie . ( GASPS )
I was looking for you at the library
because that 's where they said you were .
But , uh , you weren 't there , so I figured maybe you were here .
" Telekinesis : Unlocking the Mind . "
( STUTTERING ) No , no . Is that about , uh , hypnosis ?
Because me and my friends , we tried that .
We actually hypnotized my boy 's dog .
( CHUCKLES )
Anyway , um ...
How are you doing ?
I 'm okay .
Cool .
So you know how , um , prom is next week ?
You know ?
Um , I was wondering , if you don 't have a date already , maybe you want to go with me .
What ?
The prom . Next week .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
( GIRL LAUGHING )
TOMMY : Carrie .
Hey .
Carrie . Stop !
Please , just stop trying to trick me .
No , I 'm not trying to trick you . I 'm not tricking you .
Aren 't you with Sue Snell ?
Yeah , I 'm with Sue Snell , but she doesn 't want to go .
I 'm sorry .
( SCHOOL BELL RINGING )
( WHIMPERING )
Did one of the girls try something again ?
No .
I got invited to prom .
Really ?
( GASPS )
That 's great news .
With who ?
It 's Tommy Ross .
Wow . Tommy Ross ?
He is pretty dreamy , huh ? ( CHUCKLES )
Yeah .
I know who he goes around with .
They 're just going to trick me again .
Right ?
Maybe he really meant it .
No .
Yes , of course he did .
Why ?
Why would he want to go with me ?
Come here .
Do you know what I see ?
I see a beautiful young woman .
Maybe wear a little make-up .
Pinch your cheeks a little bit ,
put some color in there .
Curl your hair .
Stand up straight .
There you go .
DESJARDIN : Come on , Sue . ( SCHOOL BELL RINGING )
You and Chris are best friends . If you two ...
If you three are planning on playing a joke
on a lonely , defenseless girl ...
This has nothing to do with Chris .
Or you , Miss Desjardin . And for me ...
Listen , with due respect , Miss Desjardin , this is between Sue and me .
It 's kind of like a private thing .
And what is the big deal anyway ?
It 's just for one night , right ?
Famous athletes like Tim Tebow ,
he takes kids to prom all the time and everyone loves him for it .
Really ?
You 're hardly a famous athlete .
( STUTTERING ) This is a really big deal for her .
Listen . It doesn 't matter .
She said no .
So you 'll try again . Don 't .
Okay . It 's not okay .
Tommy ,
when you show up to prom with Carrie White on your arm ,
don 't you think you 're going to look the tiniest bit ridiculous ?
We don 't care how we look . Do we ?
( SCHOOL BELL RINGING )
No .
Come on .
What are you doing here ?
( CHUCKLES ) Aren 't you going to ask me in ?
What do you want ? You can 't be here .
Right to the point , huh ? Cool . About the prom .
You kind of left me hanging .
I already told you .
I know , but I was hoping that you 'd change your mind .
Girls change their mind all the time .
Why are you doing this ?
Because I want to .
You need to leave .
I 'm not leaving until you say yes .
Why is this so important to you ?
Because I think that we would have a good time .
And because I think that what you read in class was cool .
I looked up that book in the library myself .
That 's the guy who brought the temple down . Samson , right ?
Yes .
Yes , okay , I 'll go .
I have to be back by 10 : 30 .
Sure , okay . Um ...
I 'll pick you up here at 7 : 00 ?
Okay .
( CHUCKLING )
TINA : Crazy , right ? Tommy Ross and Carrie White .
( CHUCKLES )
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
Where have you been ? I was worried sick . Come on . Come inside .
I 'm sorry I 'm late , Mama . Just get inside .
Your supper 's cold . I 'm going to have to heat it up .
I didn 't know ...
You 're immodest .
I didn 't know where you were . I didn 't know .
No , Mama . I took a bus to Main Street
and I bought cloth for a dress .
You are not to go anywhere but to school and back . You know that .
Mama , before you say anything else , I 've been asked to prom .
( CLATTERING )
Mama , I 've been asked to prom .
Oh , God , why ?
It 's next Saturday and he 's a very nice boy .
And he 'll come and meet you before
and he promised to have me home by 10 : 30 .
No , no , no . I already accepted .
I know this scares you .
It scares me , too .
The other kids ,
they think I 'm weird .
But I don 't want to be .
I have to try to be a whole person .
Before it 's too late .
He 'll hurt you .
No , Mama .
No , Mama , there are bad people , but not Tommy .
He 's good . You 'll like him . He 's a very nice boy .
Boys , boys . After the blood ,
comes the boys sniffing , slobbering like dogs .
Stop it , Mama .
He 's going to paw at you until he finds where that blood smell comes from .
He 's going to take you , Carrie ,
in his car out to the wilderness ,
out where it 's cold and the roadhouses are and the whiskey .
Stop being so crazy .
You tell that boy you 're not going .
No .
We 'll move from here . We 're never going to stop moving .
You 're going to go to your closet and you 're going to pray .
You 're going to get in there and you 're going to pray for forgiveness .
No , never again , Mama !
( SCREAMS )
( CREAKING )
( WHIMPERS )
Mama , stand up .
( WHIMPERING )
Mama , stand up ! ( SCREAMING )
Mama , I 'm going .
Witch . I 'm not a witch , Mama .
There are no witches .
The devil 's got her now . Like he did before .
It 's not the devil , Mama . There are other people out there like me
who can do what I can do .
You poor child . Don 't you know he 's working through you ?
Mama , it 's inherited. it was passed down from Grandma
and it skipped you .
You know that . Maybe it came from Daddy .
He gave me a cancer . I thought you were cancer .
( SCREAMS )
That 's awful . Don 't say that . She 's lost to me .
Pray all you want , Mama , but I 'm going .
( MARGARET PRAYING INDISTINCTLY )
And nothing 's going to stop me .
( SCREAMS )
( SOBBING )
And I don 't want to talk about it anymore .
( MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO )
What are we doing ?
What does this have to do with Carrie White ?
Baby , you said you wanted us to do something about her .
( BOTH LAUGHING )
( SNORTING )
( LAUGHING )
It 's a piggy !
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
Here , piggy , piggy .
KENNY : Here , piggy , piggy .
JACKIE : It smells like shit in here .
Chris , pick one . Pick one that looks like her .
Pig 's blood for a pig .
( CHUCKLES )
( BOYS IMITATING PIGS GRUNTING )
CHRIS : That one .
BILLY : Go on .
One quick swing , all right ?
I got this .
Don 't worry , little piggy ,
Uncle Jack is going to bash your head right in .
You 're not going to feel one ...
BILLY : Shut up ! Do it already . Jesus .
( PIG SNORTING )
( WHIMPERS )
( PANTING )
I can 't .
God , you guys are such goddamn pussies .
BILLY : Shut up !
I 'm sorry , Billy .
( GRUNTS ) ( PIG SQUEALS )
( WHISTLES )
Come on , you got this .
All right , it 's just one quick slice and ...
JACKIE : Oh , my God .
( GROANS )
( PANTS )
( JACKIE LAUGHS ) Good job , baby .
( ALL LAUGHING )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
Sue . Hey , are you okay ?
( RETCHING )
( GAGS )
( VOMITS )
( PANTS )
( HUMMING )
There we go .
( CONTINUES HUMMING )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( HUMMING )
( WHISPERING ) Billy . Hurry up .
( CREAKING )
Oh , my God .
When the time comes , I 'll let you pull the rope , okay ?
Oh , I plan on it .
( GASPS )
( EXHALES DEEPLY )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( SIGHS )
TINA : Did you guys see Sue today ?
She looked awful .
I know Chris isn 't coming .
NICKI : She 's suspended .
Do you think she 'll crash ?
You never know with Chris , right ?
So , I think I 'm going to have the after-party .
No .
What do you think ? Down ?
BOTH : No .
BOTH : Yeah .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
Whoo !
( LAUGHING )
( EXHALES )
Will you pin it on me , Mama ?
Red .
I might have known it would be red .
It 's pink .
I can see your dirty pillows . Everyone will .
Breasts , Mama .
Breasts . You have them and every woman has them .
Take off that dress , Carrie .
No .
Take it off and we 'll burn it together and pray for forgiveness .
Mama , it 's modest .
Call that boy and tell him you 're not going .
You just tell him you 're sick .
I don 't want you to get hurt .
Or you could just be happy for me .
Mama , stop hurting yourself .
You know it 's not going to make me stay .
( HORN HONKING )
He 's not coming . It 's a trick .
Same as always .
He 's going to come .
They 're going to laugh at you .
They 're all going to laugh at you .
Mama , stop it .
I 'm nervous enough as it is .
( CAR DOOR OPENS )
Thank you , sir .
You see , Mama ?
You see , it 's all going to be okay .
Oh , repent . It 's not too late .
Mama , don 't ruin this for me . I 'll be home early .
I 'm going to have to tell that boy the truth
that your father took me and you were born of sin .
You 'll say nothing , Mama . And from that sin ...
MARGARET : From that sin was born another .
The worst sin .
" A man or a woman who is a witch
" among you is to be put to death .
" You are to stone them . "
( GRUNTS )
I 'm warning you , Mama .
The devil 's hand .
Please don 't do this .
There will be a judgment , Carrie .
As Jezebel fell from the tower , you too ...
( MUFFLED YELLING )
( GROANING )
( GRUNTS )
Mama , you 're not going to say another word until I 'm gone .
( KNOCK ON DOOR )
( DOGS BARKING )
( GRUNTING )
( BANGING ON DOOR )
( GRUNTS )
Mommy , I 'm sorry .
I love you .
I 'll be home early .
( BANGING ON DOOR ) ( GASPS )
( MUFFLED YELLING )
( MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO )
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
( DOOR CREAKS )
Hi .
Do I look okay ?
You look beautiful .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
Tommy , can we wait a minute ?
Yeah , sure , we can wait as long as you want .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
Are you scared ?
They 're not that bad .
Besides , I need you in there .
Dancing by myself all night , I 'd look awful silly .
( CHUCKLES )
Here , let me fix this .
I think this is supposed to go on your wrist .
There .
Are you ready ?
( MUSIC PLAYING )
God , you look handsome , Ross .
Dawson !
( BOTH LAUGHING )
Don 't worry . If they kill each other , I 'll dance with you .
Carrie , this is my best buddy , George Dawson .
And this is his girlfriend , Erika . She goes to Dover .
ERIKA : Hi .
Come on , I 'll show you the table .
I love your dress . Where did you get it ?
I made it . ( CHUCKLES )
No kidding . Really ?
Yeah . That 's amazing .
( ALL CHEERING )
( MUSIC PLAYING )
Do you want to dance ?
( SIGHS )
Or , if you want , we could wait for a slower song .
( CHUCKLING ) Yeah .
( LAUGHS )
I 'll be back .
Miss Desjardin .
You look beautiful .
I 'll let you two ladies talk .
Uh , do you want some punch ?
I heard Greg and Harry spiked it .
Really ?
( CHUCKLES ) No , I 'm just kidding .
( CHUCKLES )
You 're doing okay ?
Yeah . Yeah ?
( CELL PHONE CHIMES )
TOMMY : Listen .
Do you really have to be home so early ?
I promised .
Yeah , I know . I understand .
But , um , a bunch of people , we 're going to the Cavalier after .
That 's okay . What is ?
I know you want to hang out with your friends , and that 's ...
No .
( SLOW MUSIC PLAYING )
It 's a slow song .
No .
Yeah . Come on .
No , Tommy . I 've never danced before .
It 's okay . No , I can 't . I can 't do it .
You can 't go to prom and not have at least one dance .
I can 't .
Carrie White , will you have this dance with me ?
Come on .
( MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING )
It 's so easy . Take this hand in my hand . Like this , see ?
You 're going to put this hand on my shoulder .
And I put my hand on your hip .
Then we sway .
See , it 's easy .
You 've got nothing to worry about .
And you 're good , you 're a good learner .
And then , if you want to get fancy with it ,
we can do the Dancing With The Stars .
Yeah . No .
Yeah . Ready ? Look .
( BOTH CHUCKLING )
To the first one .
This is fun , right ? ( BOTH CHUCKLING )
Tommy , why am I here ?
Because I invited you .
But why ?
Carrie , we 're here .
We 're at prom . I 'm having such a great time with you .
You are ?
( CHUCKLING ) Yeah .
And I hope that you 're having a good time with me .
Yeah .
So , what do you say we dance a little longer ,
and then we see which poor fool they crown King and Queen ,
and then we go to the Cavalier ? ( BOTH CHUCKLE )
And I 'll have you home by 10 : 30 . How does that sound to you ?
Yeah . Yeah ?
Maybe 11 : 00 .
Whatever you want .
( CARRIE CHUCKLES )
CARRIE : 11 : 00 .
( CREAKING )
( GRUNTS )
( GRUNTING )
( CROWD CHEERING )
ERNIE : All right , everyone , take your seats . Take your seats .
It 's now time to vote for your King
and Queen of the prom . All right . ( ALL CHEERING )
Ballots are on the table . Everyone gets their own , please .
Guys , take your seats .
Here .
Make an " X " beside the candidate of your choice .
Let 's have the best prom ever .
Whoo !
All right .
Tommy , we 're on here .
Don 't you want to be on there ?
Do you ?
Why not ?
If we win , the only thing that happens is
we have to go up there on those thrones ,
wave a scepter around while they play the school song ,
and then , uh , do a little dance so everyone can see how idiotic we look .
They are beautiful .
You 're beautiful .
So , who do we vote for ?
( CHUCKLES ) I guess they 're more your crowd than mine .
I don 't really have a crowd .
Well , I think we vote for ourselves , right ?
No . No , don 't vote for us .
To the devil with false modesty .
To the devil .
( LAUGHS )
Hurt yourself ? No .
To my boy , George Dawson , to the Fearsome Four ,
Mike , Matt , Brian , and Brad . I 'm going to miss you guys .
All set ? TOMMY : Oh , yeah .
Good luck , kids . You 've got my vote .
More ballots for you .
Hey , girl .
( CELL PHONE BUZZING )
( BEEPS )
( ENGINE STARTS )
( ALL CHEERING )
Here you go .
As soon as that bucket goes , we run .
We don 't stick around for the laughs or the screams or anything .
All right ?
BILLY : You got it ?
Are you listening ? Hey .
What ? When they get up there ,
what 's happening ? You 're pulling the rope and when the ...
Shut up so I can hear . Hey . Listen to me . Listen .
If you get caught and you say anything about what we did ,
I will fucking kill you .
This isn 't what you bitches did in the shower .
This is criminal assault .
This is fucking jail time if we 're caught .
I get it .
( BRAKES SCREECH )
( PANTING )
Hey . Whatever happens tonight , you 're Queen , okay ?
And the results are in . And it was very , very close .
ERNIE : A drum roll , please .
( DRUM ROLL )
By one vote , our winners are ...
Tommy Ross and Carrie White !
( EXHALES )
( AUDIENCE APPLAUDS )
( MUSIC PLAYING )
Come on .
BOY : Way to go , Carrie .
( LAUGHING )
Heather , where 's Chris ?
What are you talking about ? She 's not here .
( CROWD CHEERING )
Hey , what 's wrong ? Come on , go . You can do this .
We are fucking doing this . It 's too late to go back now .
ERNIE : Ewen High ...
I give you your newly crowned King and Queen of the prom ,
Tommy Ross and Carrie White .
Pull it ! Shut up , Billy !
Chris . Sue ?
( GRUNTS )
( GASPS )
DESJARDIN : Sue .
What are you doing ? Come on . Come on , let 's go .
No ! Miss Desjardin , it 's not me . It 's Chris .
Pull it , Billy , pull it !
Don 't ruin this for Carrie .
It 's not me ! Come on . Out .
Let her have this . No , wait !
( GRUNTS )
( GASPS )
( ALL GASP )
( SHUDDERING )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
( SHUDDERS )
What the hell ?
ALL : ( CHANTING ) Plug it up !
( SOBBING ) Please help me !
( ALL LAUGHING )
Carrie , wait . Carrie .
( SOBBING ) Help me .
No !
( LAUGHING )
Freak ! Freak ! Come on .
( ALL LAUGHING )
Carrie , come on .
( ALL GASP )
( GIRL SCREAMS )
Tommy .
( WHIMPERING )
( SOBBING ) Tommy , no .
No .
( ENGINE REVVING ) CHRIS : Fuck .
You have an inch .
BILLY : Yeah . Come on .
Go , go . Come on .
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLING )
Come on . Are you seeing this ?
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Wait . Come on .
( SCREAMING )
There 's been an explosion .
Don 't panic !
( ALL SCREAMING )
Bleachers !
( GRUNTS )
( ALL SCREAMING )
( GROANS )
( SCREAMING )
LIZZY : We have to get to the door .
Nicki !
( BOTH SCREAM )
Lizzy ! Nicki !
( BOTH SCREAMING )
Come on ! We got to go ! DESJARDIN : Okay .
ULMANN : Tina , come on !
We 're all going to die !
Come on !
( GRUNTS )
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLING )
( SCREAMING )
( CHOKING )
( GROANING )
( COUGHING )
( SIRENS WAILING )
( PANTING )
( ENGINE REVVING )
( SIREN WAILING )
What are you doing ? What are you doing ?
Nothing . Do you think this is a fucking game ?
Shut up .
What are we going to do ?
We 're going to leave town and we 're never going to come back .
( SOBBING )
Okay ? It 's okay . It 's going to be okay .
Okay .
( SIREN WAILING )
( BRAKES SCREECHING )
Oh , my God ! Watch out !
( GROANING )
( TIRES SCREECHING )
Shit town !
CHRIS : Go , move !
( TIRES SCREECHING )
Oh , my God .
It 's Carrie .
Run her down .
Kill her .
Kill her , Billy . Kill her , Billy ! Kill her !
Shut up ! I got this .
Come on !
( SCREAMING )
( BOTH GROAN ) ( GLASS SHATTERING )
( GROANING )
Billy ?
No .
( GRUNTS )
( GASPING )
( SOBBING )
( ENGINE REVVING )
( GROANING )
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLING )
( INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS )
( SIREN WAILING )
( SOBBING )
Mommy . Mommy . Mommy .
Mama ?
( CREAKING )
Mama !
No .
( SOBBING ) No .
I 'm so sorry .
Mama ?
( CREAKING ) ( GASPS )
Oh , Mama .
Mama , you were right .
They laughed at me , Mommy .
They all laughed at me .
I knew they 'd hurt my little girl .
I should have killed myself when he put it in me .
We slept in the same bed ,
lived together sinlessly .
Then one night , I saw him look at me in that way .
And we got down on our knees to pray for strength .
And that 's when he took me .
No , Mama . I don 't want to hear it .
And I liked it . Mama , no .
I should have given you to God when you were born , but ...
I was weak .
And I loved you so much .
And I said , " God ,
" let me keep my little girl .
" Let me keep her . "
Let 's pray .
Yes , Mama .
Yes , we 'll pray .
I 'll be the preacher . You 'll be my congregation .
" Our Father , Who art in heaven ,
" hallowed be Thy name .
" Thy kingdom come ,
" Thy will be done
" on earth
" as it is in heaven . "
Mama !
( SHRIEKS )
( GROANS )
Mama , please .
No , Mama . Mama , please .
This isn 't your fault , Carrie . It 's mine .
Mommy , this isn 't right . You know the devil never dies .
He keeps coming back . You 've got to keep killin ' him .
No , Mama . Over and over again .
Mama , please . Mama !
No !
No , Mama . ( SCREAMS )
( GRUNTING )
Mama , stop it !
( SCREAMS )
( YELLING )
( PANTING )
Carrie . I 'm sorry .
Carrie !
( BOTH SCREAM )
( GRUNTING )
( GROANING )
( GASPING )
( BOTH GRUNT )
Okay .
It 's okay .
( SHUSHING )
It 's okay . No one 's going to hurt you .
No one 's going to hurt you .
( SOBBING )
( DOOR CREAKING )
SUE : Carrie ?
Let me help you , Carrie .
Why couldn 't you leave me alone ?
I 'm sorry .
( CHOKING )
Look what you turned me into .
Don 't hurt me , Carrie .
Why not ?
I 've been hurt my whole life .
( CHOKING )
I killed my mom .
I want her back .
I 'm scared .
( RUMBLING )
We 've got to get out of here !
Give me your hand . Give me your hand .
Come on !
It 's a girl . What ?
You don 't know ?
Oh , my God .
Get out !
It 's okay .
( THUNDER RUMBLES )
( GROANS )
WOMAN : You 're doing great . That 's just another contraction .
Okay .
Sue , do me a favor and push .
( GROANS )
No , something doesn 't feel right . It doesn 't feel right .
Come on now , breathe . Try again , Sue . Try again .
MAN : Everything 's okay .
There we go . Ready ?
( SHRIEKS )
It hurts ! Please help me ! ( SOBBING )
MAN : Just lay back , okay , Sue ?
There you go .
WOMAN : Almost there .
Is it normal ?
All right , just push ! Everything 's gonna be okay .
( MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY )
( SCREAMING )
WOMAN : Hold her still !
Sue , push !
MAN : Sue , I need you to breathe !
Now , get ready for the next one .
( PANTING )
Push ! You can do it ! Come on !
( GROANS )
( PANTING )
( SCREAMING )
Wake up , baby !
It 's okay , it 's okay . I gotcha . ( SHUSHING )
It 's over , baby ! It 's over ! ( CONTINUES SCREAMING )
Sue , you 're all right !
You 're all right !
Baby , wake up !
( SINGING ) I can hardly make you mine
Tell it to you all the time
At the end of a long day and when I wake
If you could just give me a sign
We could leave it all behind
Stop taking the long way before we play
I don 't think I can make it and I know you 're the one
Staring into the tears like a loaded gun
Well , I can hardly make you mine
Tell it to you all the time
But you never wanted , but you had to take
So I can never give you up
I guess it 's ' cause it 's just a crush
Before the end of a long day and then I wake
But I know you 're not the one or the only
But we both know what it 's like to be lonely
Well , these fantasies , they left us lonely
Boy , just bring all your love back to me
I guess for now this is how it 'll be
I don 't think I can make it Oh , you 're the one
Staring into the tears like a loaded gun